<dashboard>
  <label>Domain Typo Squatting</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <title>DNStwist</title>
      <html>
        Adversaries will often attempt to confuse targets by creating malicious domains that are visually similar to a legitimate domain. These malicous domains  intentiaonally use typos, homoglyphs, and common dictionary words to exploit users.  Lenny Zeltser has a wonderful <a href="https://zeltser.com/domain-name-variations-in-phishing/">blog post</a> that discusses those methods in more detail. A great method for detecting these camoflagued domains is using a python tool named dnstwist, a "domain name permutation engine".  This app supplies an example output of dnstwist  tool and brief instructions on how to setup dnstwist and splunk in your environment

        Install DNS twist using the instructions from dnstwist's <a href="https://github.com/elceef/dnstwist">github page</a>. Once installed make sure you record the path to the dictionaries or execution path. In this example we have used all of the dnstwist options for data gathering and outp<code>dnstwist trump.com -w -g -b -s -m -c -t 100 -d english.dict</code> <img style="border: gray 1px solid;" src="/static/app/SA-TI_Showcase/images/dnstwist.png"/>
      </html>
    </panel>
    <panel>
      <title>dnstwist and Splunk</title>
      <html>
        Once you are familar with using dnstwist and its output look at ingesting that data into Splunk
            <ol>
          <li>Using the domain you are attempting to emulate, create a cronjob that outputs the results of dnstwist into a CSV on a daily or weekly schedule</li>
            <center>
            <img style="border: gray 1px solid;" src="/static/app/SA-TI_Showcase/images/cronjob.png"/>
          </center>
            <li>Configure Splunk to ingest the output of dnstwist csv as a <a href="https://docs.splunk.com/Documentation/Splunk/latest/PivotTutorial/AddlookupfilestoSplunk">lookup table</a>
          </li>
            <li>Use this lookup table with saved searches to find malicious domains in your network</li>
        </ol>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <table>
        <title>Sample data harvested from dnstwist using trump.com as an example</title>
        <search>
          <query>|inputlookup dnstwist.csv| fields domain-name dns-mx geoip-country whois-created whois-updated</query>
          <earliest>0</earliest>
          <latest></latest>
        </search>
        <option name="count">10</option>
        <option name="rowNumbers">false</option>
        <option name="wrap">true</option>
      </table>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>